<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="Better Economy" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Fixes all problems with the economy" />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--LongDescription Value="This is a long description" /-->
	<LongDescription>
The goal of the mod is to fix bugs in the original game while minimizing deviation from the original gameplay mechanics.
This mod doesn’t make the game harder or easier; it makes your actions more meaningful.

For example, with the mod, if you set low commercial taxes, your companies will prosper and bring you significant profits in the distant future. Alternatively, you can raise taxes to gain money immediately, but this risks company collapses in the future. (In contrast, due to bugs in the original game, companies can collapse randomly.)

Ultimately, it’s not just a mod but a patch with many changes that should have been part of the game. (And I hope they will be in the future.)

Fixes:
- Fixed a bug where companies would randomly leave the city.
- Companies now rely solely on their funds to level up buildings (previously, they could level up even if heavily in debt).
- Fixed building upkeep charges so they subtract money from the renter instead of adding it.
- Fixed tax calculations for processing companies.
- Fixed garbage fees, which were previously collected at 16x the intended amount.

This mod alters the behavior of many systems, so any other mods that affect the economy, even slightly, are incompatible with it.

The mod works with old cities, but there’s a high chance that your city is already economically broken due to bugs. The city’s economy will stabilize, but it may take several hours of real time at 3x speed.

	</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/better-economy.1724695/" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="1.0.0" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.2.*" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<ChangeLog>
**v1.0.0**
- Initial version

	</ChangeLog>
	<!--External link. supported types are discord, github, youtube, twitch, x, paypal, patreon-->
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/nucleartux/CS2BetterEconomy" />
	<ExternalLink Type="patreon" Url="https://patreon.com/adrov" />
	<ExternalLink Type="paypal" Url="https://paypal.me/iadrov" />
</Publish>
